{"0":{"question":" What is the name for the Jewish New Year?","choices":["Hanukkah","Yom Kippur","Kwanza","Rosh Hashanah"],"correct_answer":"Rosh Hashanah"},"1":{"question":"How many blue stripes are there on the U.S. flag?","choices":["6","7","13","0"],"correct_answer":"0"},"2":{"question":"Which one of these characters is not friends with Harry Potter?","choices":["Ron Weasley","Neville Longbottom","Draco Malfoy","Hermione Granger"],"correct_answer":"Draco Malfoy"},"3":{"question":"What is the color of Donald Duck’s bowtie?","choices":["Red","Yellow","Blue","White"],"correct_answer":"Red"},"4":{"question":"What was the name of the band Lionel Richie was a part of?","choices":["King Harvest","Spectrums","Commodores","The Marshall Tucker Band"],"correct_answer":"Commodores"},"5":{"question":"Which animal does not appear in the Chinese zodiac?","choices":["Dragon","Rabbit","Dog","Hummingbird"],"correct_answer":"Hummingbird"},"6":{"question":"Which country held the 2016 Summer Olympics?","choices":["China","Ireland","Brazil","Italy"],"correct_answer":"Brazil"},"7":{"question":"Which planet is the hottest?","choices":["Venus","Saturn","Mercury","Mars"],"correct_answer":"Venus"},"8":{"question":"Who was the only U.S. President to resign?","choices":["Herbert Hoover","Richard Nixon","George W. Bush","Barack Obama"],"correct_answer":"Nixon"},"9":{"question":"What does the “D” in “D-Day” stand for?","choices":["Dooms","Dark","Denmark ","Dunkirk"],"correct_answer":"Dunkirk"},"10":{"question":"In which city can you find the Liberty Bell?","choices":["Washington, D.C.","Boston","Philadelphia","Manhattan "],"correct_answer":"Philadelphia"},"11":{"question":"In Pirates of the Caribbean, what was the name of Captain Jack Sparrow’s ship?","choices":["The Marauder","The Black Pearl","The Black Python","The Slytherin"],"correct_answer":"The Black Pearl"},"12":{"question":"According to Forrest Gump, “life was like…”","choices":["A bag of lemons","A handful of roses","A lollipop","A box of chocolates"],"correct_answer":"A box of chocolates"},"13":{"question":"Linda and Bob from Bob’s Burgers have 3 kids. Which one of these characters is not one of them?","choices":["Louise","Gene","Jimmy","Tina"],"correct_answer":"Jimmy"},"14":{"question":"The British band One Direction (rip) was made up of Harry, Louis, Niall, Zayn, and…","choices":["Paul","Callum","Kevin","Liam"],"correct_answer":"Liam"},"15":{"question":"What is the rarest blood type?","choices":["Rh-Null","A - Positive","A-Negative","B - Positive","B-Negative","AB - Positive","AB-Negative","O - Positive","O-Negative"],"correct_answer":"AB-Negative"},"16":{"question":"Holly Golightly is a character in which film?","choices":["Breakfast at Tiffanys","Pretty In Pink","Funny Face","Singing In The Rain"],"correct_answer":"Breakfast at Tiffanys"},"17":{"question":"In The Wizard of Oz, the Tin Man wanted to see the Wizard about getting…","choices":["A brain","An oil can","A dog","A heart"],"correct_answer":"A heart"},"18":{"question":"Which U.S. state is known as the sunflower state?","choices":["Florida","California","Maine","Kansas"],"correct_answer":"Kansas"},"19":{"question":"Which one of these characters aren’t a part of the Friends group?","choices":["Rachel","Joey","Gunther","Monica"],"correct_answer":"Gunther"},"20":{"question":"How many bones are there in the human body?","choices":["206","205","201","209"],"correct_answer":"206"},"21":{"question":"Which famous singer released a song called “Adore You”?","choices":["Harry Styles","Dua Lipa","Halsey","Shawn Mendes"],"correct_answer":"Harry Styles"},"22":{"question":"Fe is the chemical symbol for…","choices":["Zinc","Hydrogen","Fluorine","Iron"],"correct_answer":"Iron"},"23":{"question":"How old do you have to be to enter in the hunger games?","choices":["12","11","10","15"],"correct_answer":"12"},"24":{"question":"What language is the most spoken worldwide?","choices":["Chinese","Spanish","Arabic","English"],"correct_answer":"Chinese"},"25":{"question":"What year did Barbie come out?","choices":["1958","1959","1956","1961"],"correct_answer":"1959"},"26":{"question":"What is Shakespeare’s shortest tragedy?","choices":["Macbeth","Hamlet","Romeo & Juliet","Othello"],"correct_answer":"Macbeth"},"27":{"question":"What is the #1 cookie in the U.S.?","choices":["Chips Ahoy!","Milano","Girl Scout Thin Mints","Oreo"],"correct_answer":"Oreo"},"28":{"question":"How many hearts does an octopus have?","choices":["1","2","3","4"],"correct_answer":"3"},"29":{"question":"Who wrote The Scarlett Letter?","choices":["Shakespeare","Stephen King","Nathanial Hawthorne","Ernest Hemingway"],"correct_answer":"Nathanial Hawthorne"},"30":{"question":"Which social media platform came out in 2003?","choices":["Myspace","Twitter","Facebook","Tumblr"],"correct_answer":"Myspace"},"31":{"question":"Which planet in our solar system is the largest?","choices":["Jupiter","Saturn","Neptune","Earth"],"correct_answer":"Jupiter"},"32":{"question":"The Powerpuff Girls are 3 distinct colors. What are they?","choices":["Red, yellow, green","Yellow, blue, green","Blue, green, red","Green, purple, orange"],"correct_answer":"Blue, green, red"},"33":{"question":"Which boyband sings the song “I Want It That Way”?","choices":["One Direction","Backstreet Boys","NSYNC","New Kids On The Block"],"correct_answer":"Backstreet Boys"},"34":{"question":"Who painted the Sistine Chapel ceiling?","choices":["Picasso","Da Vinci","Michelangelo","Van Gogh"],"correct_answer":"Michelangelo"},"35":{"question":"In which state did the Salem Witch Trials take place?","choices":["Washington","Virginia","Massachusetts","Pennsylvania"],"correct_answer":"Massachusetts"},"36":{"question":"Which ocean is the largest?","choices":["Indian","Pacific","Atlantic","Arctic"],"correct_answer":"Pacific"},"37":{"question":"Which New York City building is the tallest:","choices":["Empire State Building","Bank of America Tower","One World Trade Center","Statue of Liberty"],"correct_answer":"World Trade Center"},"38":{"question":"What does the “E” in Chuck E. Cheese stand for?","choices":["Ernest","Edward","Entertainment","Extra"],"correct_answer":"Entertainment"},"39":{"question":"Which country gifted the Statue of Liberty to the U.S.?","choices":["Germany","China","France","Italy"],"correct_answer":"France"},"40":{"question":"Who painted the Mona Lisa?","choices":["Van Gogh","da Vinci","Picasso","Monet"],"correct_answer":"da Vinci"},"41":{"question":"In which city were Anne Frank and her family in hiding?","choices":["Paris","Amsterdam","Brussels","Frankfurt"],"correct_answer":"Amsterdam"},"42":{"question":"There are 4 best friends in the TV show Pretty Little Liars: Hanna, Emily, Aria, and…","choices":["Mona","Charlie","Alison","Spencer"],"correct_answer":"Spencer"},"43":{"question":"In which decade does the Netflix series Stranger Things take place?","choices":["‘70s","‘80s","‘90s","early 2000s"],"correct_answer":"’80s"},"44":{"question":"Which country consumes the most chocolate?","choices":["Spain","Germany","North America","Switzerland"],"correct_answer":"Switzerland"},"45":{"question":"What is Sodium Chloride?","choices":["Salt","Sugar","Chlorine","Bleach"],"correct_answer":"Salt"},"46":{"question":"Which astrological sign is a crab?","choices":["Pisces","Aquarius","Cancer","Virgo"],"correct_answer":"Cancer"},"47":{"question":"In the Bible, how does the Virgin Mary learn of her pregnancy with baby Jesus?","choices":["God tells her","the angel Gabriel tells her","she has a dream about it","a doctor tells her"],"correct_answer":"the angel Gabriel tells her"},"48":{"question":"Who, in the Harry Potter series, is Tom Riddle?","choices":["a student in Harry’s class","a professor at Hogwarts","Harry’s birth father","Voldemort"],"correct_answer":"Voldemort"},"49":{"question":"The movie The Social Network is about which social media platform:","choices":["Facebook","Myspace","Instagram","Twitter"],"correct_answer":"Facebook"},"50":{"question":"Who wrote the songs for The Lion King? ","choices":["Elton John","Phil Collins","Celine Dion","Stevie Wonder"],"correct_answer":"Elton John"},"51":{"question":"How many daughters does Barack Obama have?","choices":["0","1","2","3"],"correct_answer":"2"},"52":{"question":"Which Disney princess sings “Just Around The Riverbend”?","choices":["Snow White","Pocahontas","Elsa","Belle"],"correct_answer":"Pocahontas"},"53":{"question":"Which biblical narrative is connected to Palm Sunday?","choices":["Jesus’ entry into Jerusalem","Jesus’ resurrection","Jesus feeding the thousands","Nothing, it just means to go to church on Sunday/the day of rest"],"correct_answer":"Jesus’ entry into Jerusalem"},"54":{"question":"In Harry Potter and the Sorcerer’s Stone, who gives Harry the invisibility cloak?","choices":["Ron","Snape","Dumbledore","No one, he just finds it"],"correct_answer":"Dumbledore"},"55":{"question":"How many burroughs are there in New York City?","choices":["4","5","6","10"],"correct_answer":"5"},"56":{"question":"In the U.S. version of The Office, Michael Scott burns his foot on:","choices":["hot water","pavement/cement","rocks on fire","a George Foreman Grill"],"correct_answer":"George Foreman Grill"},"57":{"question":"The superstitution believes that when the groundhog sees his shadow, it means:","choices":["early spring","6 more weeks of winter","it’s going to rain","a tornado is coming"],"correct_answer":"6 more weeks of winter"},"58":{"question":"What is the longest river in the world?","choices":["Amazon","Congo","Nile","Hudson"],"correct_answer":"Nile River"},"59":{"question":"How many days are in February during a leap year?","choices":["28","29","30","31"],"correct_answer":"29"},"60":{"question":"How many degrees are in a circle?","choices":["360","180","150","359"],"correct_answer":"360 degrees"},"61":{"question":"Which city is known as the City of Love?","choices":["Rome","Barcelona","New York City","Paris"],"correct_answer":"Paris"},"62":{"question":"As an adult, how many teeth should you have in your mouth?","choices":["35","32","30","42"],"correct_answer":"32"},"63":{"question":"What was the name of the boy who won Willy Wonka’s factory?","choices":["Charlie Baxter","Charlie Brown","Charlie Bones","Charlie Bucket"],"correct_answer":"Charlie Bucket"},"64":{"question":"Edward Scissorhands is known for cutting:","choices":["hair","bushes","clothes","everything"],"correct_answer":"everything"},"65":{"question":"In which city would you find the Fisherman’s Bastion?","choices":["Rome","Budapest","Barcelona","Athens"],"correct_answer":"Budapest"},"66":{"question":"Which U.S. president doesn’t/didn’t have a dog in the White House?","choices":["Trump","Obama","Bush","Lincoln"],"correct_answer":"Trump"},"67":{"question":"What does the “U” stand for in “UFO”?","choices":["Unidentified","Under","United","Unique"],"correct_answer":"Unidentified"},"68":{"question":"Which U.S. state is known as “America’s Dairyland”?","choices":["Minnesota","Iowa","Pennsylvania","Wisconsin"],"correct_answer":"Wisconsin"},"69":{"question":"Usher found a young boy singing on YouTube and made him into a famous singer. What’s that kid’s name?","choices":["Niall Horan","Jaden Smith","Shawn Mendes","Justin Bieber"],"correct_answer":"Justin Bieber"},"70":{"question":"Which Olympic sport is Michael Phelps known for?","choices":["Snowboarding","Skiing","Running","Swimming"],"correct_answer":"Swimming"},"71":{"question":"What is the complementary color of green?","choices":["blue","yellow","red","purple"],"correct_answer":"Red"},"72":{"question":"Han Solo is a character from which movie series:","choices":["Harry Potter","Star Wars","Lord of the Rings","Indiana Jones"],"correct_answer":"Star Wars"},"73":{"question":"In Men and Black, what are the two FBI agents hunting?","choices":["serial killers","ghosts","aliens","time travelers"],"correct_answer":"Aliens"},"74":{"question":"The most recent seasons of American Idol have the judges Katy Perry, Lionel Richie, and…","choices":["Trace Adkins","Luke Bryan","Blake Shelton","Keith Urban"],"correct_answer":"Luke Bryan"},"75":{"question":"How many Harry Potter books are there?","choices":["7","8","6","10"],"correct_answer":"7"},"76":{"question":"What breed is dog is the most popular in the U.S.?","choices":["Pug","Dalmatian","Beagle","Golden Retriever"],"correct_answer":"Golden Retriever"},"77":{"question":"Which rapper was known for his album Blue Slide Park?","choices":["J Cole","Post Malone","Eminem","Mac Miller"],"correct_answer":"Mac Miller"},"78":{"question":"How many sides does a hexagon have?","choices":["5","6","7","8"],"correct_answer":"6"},"79":{"question":"In which city was Ferris Bueller’s Day Off filmed?","choices":["Pittsburgh","Chicago","NYC","San Francisco"],"correct_answer":"Chicago"},"80":{"question":"The UK is made up of the following countries: England, Ireland, Wales, and…","choices":["France","Hungary","Scotland","Austria"],"correct_answer":"Scotland"},"81":{"question":"How many elements are there on the periodic table?","choices":["112","118","120","143"],"correct_answer":"118"},"82":{"question":"Where is the United Nations Headquarters?","choices":["D.C.","NYC","Philadelphia","Orlando"],"correct_answer":"NYC"},"83":{"question":"What famous singer sings with Taylor Swift in her song “Me!”?","choices":["Brendan Urie","Shawn Mendes","Ellie Goulding","Halsey"],"correct_answer":"Brendan Urie"},"84":{"question":"In what year did women get the right to vote?","choices":["1910","1920","1930","1940"],"correct_answer":"1920"},"85":{"question":"Where in the United States is the largest aquarium?","choices":["New Jersey","Maine","California","Georgia"],"correct_answer":"Georgia"},"86":{"question":"There are 5 great lakes in the United States: Lake Michigan, Lake Superior, Lake Ontario, Lake Erie, and…","choices":["Lake Huron","Lake Hartwell","Lake Tahoe","Great Bear Lake"],"correct_answer":"Lake Huron"},"87":{"question":"Neil Armstrong was the first man…","choices":["on Mars","on a spacecraft alone","on the Moon","to travel to the sun"],"correct_answer":"On the Moon"},"88":{"question":"What does “FBI” stand for?","choices":["Female Body Inspector","Federal Bureau of Investigation","Federal Business of Investigation","Federal Bureau of Inspection"],"correct_answer":"Federal Bureau of Investigation"},"89":{"question":"What is the deadliest snake?","choices":["Python","Cobra","Cobra","Black Mamba"],"correct_answer":"Black Mamba"},"90":{"question":"In The Office, what object of Dwight’s does Jim put in jello?","choices":["computer mouse","wallet","stapler","coffee mug"],"correct_answer":"Stapler"},"91":{"question":"In Friends, how many times has Ross been married?","choices":["only once","3 times","twice","more than 3 times"],"correct_answer":"3 times"},"92":{"question":"What is a group of lions called?","choices":["Squad","Pack","Herd","Pride"],"correct_answer":"Pride"},"93":{"question":"How many keys are on a piano?","choices":["86","87","88","89"],"correct_answer":"88"},"94":{"question":"What was the name of the Greek mythological woman who had snakes for hair?","choices":["Pandora","Helen","Cassiopeia","Medusa"],"correct_answer":"Medusa"},"95":{"question":"What do you call a baby goat?","choices":["Kid","Goatee","Child","Baby Goat"],"correct_answer":"Kid"},"96":{"question":"According to Phineas and Ferb, there are __ days of summer vacation?","choices":["90","103","104","110"],"correct_answer":"104"},"97":{"question":"What is the most populous city in Canada?","choices":["Toronto","Ontario","Quebec","Vancouver"],"correct_answer":"Toronto"},"98":{"question":"The Da Vinci Code opens with a murder in which museum:","choices":["The Guggenheim","The Louvre","The Van Gogh museum","The Metropolitan Museum of Art"],"correct_answer":"the Louvre"},"99":{"question":"From which TV show is the family of Roses: Johnny, Moira, David, and Alexis?","choices":["Bob’s Burgers","Schitt’s Creek","Parenthood","7th Heaven "],"correct_answer":"Schitt’s Creek "},"100":{"question":"After The Simpsons, what is the longest running TV show?","choices":["Law & Order","Grey’s Anatomy","Criminal Minds","NCIS"],"correct_answer":"Law & Order"},"101":{"question":"Which Disney princess sings “A Dream Is A Wish Your Heart Makes”?","choices":["Belle","Cinderella","Jasmine","Sleeping Beauty"],"correct_answer":"Cinderella"},"102":{"question":"How often does the moon orbit the Earth?","choices":["every 7 days","every 27 days","every 30 days","every 365 days"],"correct_answer":"every 27 days"},"103":{"question":"In Greek Mythology, who is the Queen of the Underworld?","choices":["Pandora","Medusa","Helen","Persephone"],"correct_answer":"Persephone"},"104":{"question":"How many points are a touchdown worth?","choices":["5","6","7","8"],"correct_answer":"6"},"105":{"question":"How many feet are in a mile?","choices":["1,037","5,288","5,280","6,201"],"correct_answer":"5,280 feet"},"106":{"question":"Question: Where is the Oval Office located in the White House?","choices":["North Wing","South Wing","East Wing","West Wing"],"correct_answer":"West Wing"},"107":{"question":"At what temperature (Fahrenheit) does water freeze at?","choices":["32 degrees","40 degrees","-10 degrees","0 degrees"],"correct_answer":"32 degrees"},"108":{"question":"Where in Pennsylvania is The Office based?","choices":["Philadelphia","Pittsburgh","Scranton","Lancaster"],"correct_answer":"Scranton"},"109":{"question":"In the movie Good Will Hunting, which college does Skylar attend?","choices":["Harvard","Yale","Columbia","UCLA"],"correct_answer":"Harvard"},"110":{"question":"Where in California is Disneyland located?","choices":["Malibu","Huntington Beach","Los Angeles","Anaheim"],"correct_answer":"Anaheim"},"111":{"question":"“I see dead people,” is a line from which horror film…","choices":["The Sixth Sense","The Grudge","The Shining","The Exorcist "],"correct_answer":"The Sixth Sense"},"112":{"question":"Who founded Microsoft?","choices":["Bill Hader","Steve Jobs","Bill Gates","Mark Zuckerberg"],"correct_answer":"Bill Gates"},"113":{"question":"In which city was the movie National Treasure filmed?","choices":["Washington D.C.","NYC","Philadelphia","Roanoke"],"correct_answer":"Philadelphia"},"114":{"question":"Which classic novel has the line “Stay Gold, Ponyboy”?","choices":["The Catcher in the Rye","1984","The Outsiders","Catch-22"],"correct_answer":"The Outsiders"},"115":{"question":"What was the name of Harry Potter’s pet owl?","choices":["Hedwig","Luna","Dobby","Fluffy"],"correct_answer":"Hedwig"},"116":{"question":"Which Disney princess had 3 fairy godmothers?","choices":["Cinderella","Snow White","Sleeping Beauty","Jasmine"],"correct_answer":"Sleeping Beauty"},"117":{"question":"Which band came back together in 2019?","choices":["The Naked Brothers Band","The Jonas Brothers","One Direction","The Beatles"],"correct_answer":"The Jonas Brothers"},"118":{"question":"Steve Jobs is known for wearing a black…","choices":["button-down shirt","t-shirt","turtleneck","blazer"],"correct_answer":"Turtleneck"},"119":{"question":"In which movie does Anne Hathaway play a poor, homeless woman?","choices":["The Devil Wears Prada","Les Miserables","The Princess Diaries","Ella Enchanted "],"correct_answer":"Les Miserables"},"120":{"question":"The movie 10 Things I Hate About You was based on which play by Shakespeare:","choices":["Taming of the Shrew","Hamlet","Romeo and Juliet","A Midsummer Night’s Dream"],"correct_answer":"The Taming of the Shrew"},"121":{"question":"Where does Nathan’s Hot Dog Eating Contest take place?","choices":["Coney Island","Miami Beach","Mall of America","Orlando"],"correct_answer":"Coney Island"},"122":{"question":"What age did Amy Winehouse, Janis Joplin, and Jimi Hendrix die?","choices":["26","27","29","30"],"correct_answer":"27"},"123":{"question":"Which two planets in our solar system are known as “ice giants”?","choices":["Neptune and Jupiter","Uranus and Pluto","Pluto and Jupiter","Neptune and Uranus"],"correct_answer":"Neptune + Uranus"},"124":{"question":"What country is Prague in?","choices":["Hungary","Austria","Czech Republic","Germany"],"correct_answer":"Czech Republic"},"125":{"question":"What is the name of the actress in Funny Face, Sabrina and Roman Holiday?","choices":["Audrey Hepburn","Natalie Wood","Marilyn Monroe","Grace Kelly"],"correct_answer":"Audrey Hepburn"},"126":{"question":"Which poet wrote the poem “The Raven”? ","choices":["Robert Frost","Edgar Allen Poe","Walt Whitman","Sylvia Plath"],"correct_answer":"Edgar Allen Poe"},"127":{"question":"How many ribs are in the human body?","choices":["16","24","19","29"],"correct_answer":"24"},"128":{"question":"Who was the 16th president of the United States?","choices":["Lincoln","Nixon","Jackson","Madison"],"correct_answer":"Lincoln"},"129":{"question":"Who wrote the novel Slaughterhouse-Five?","choices":["Kurt Vonnegut","Stephen King","J.D. Salinger","Harper Lee"],"correct_answer":"Kurt Vonnegut"},"130":{"question":"In The Office, what was the food that Dwight grew on his farm?","choices":["pumpkins","beets","onions","potatoes"],"correct_answer":"beets"},"131":{"question":"What animal is associated with ancient Egypt?","choices":["lion","cat","hummingbird","rabbit"],"correct_answer":"cat"},"132":{"question":"In 2016, a musician won the Nobel Peace Prize for Literature. Who was it?","choices":["Lenny Kravitz","Eric Clapton","Bob Dylan","Elton John"],"correct_answer":"Bob Dylan"},"133":{"question":"How many time zones are there in the world?","choices":["7","24","23","9"],"correct_answer":"24"},"134":{"question":"What was the name of the movie that featured Matthew McConaughey, Michael Caine, Anne Hathaway, John Lithgow, and Matt Damon?","choices":["Flight Plan","The Martian ","Interstellar","Ad Astra"],"correct_answer":"Interstellar"},"135":{"question":"How many rings are there in the Olympic symbol?","choices":["5","7","4","9"],"correct_answer":"5"},"136":{"question":"Twilight was both a book and a movie, with the main character Bella Swan being pulled into two different love directions with Edward Cullen and….","choices":["Jasper Hale","Jacob Black","Billy Black","Dr. Cullen"],"correct_answer":"Jacob Black"},"137":{"question":"What is celebrated on December 26th?","choices":["the day after Christmas","Harvest Day","Boxing Day","National Dog Day"],"correct_answer":"Boxing Day"},"138":{"question":"What is the name of the second American astronaut to step foot on the moon?","choices":["Buzz Aldrin","Neil Armstrong","Alan Bean","James Irwin"],"correct_answer":"Buzz Aldrin"},"139":{"question":"How many eyes does a spider have?","choices":["8","9","10","2"],"correct_answer":"8"},"140":{"question":"What is the first book of the Old Testament in the Bible?","choices":["Matthew","Proverbs","Genesis","Exodus"],"correct_answer":"Genesis"},"141":{"question":"Which founding father is known for his large handwriting on the Declaration of Independence?","choices":["John Hancock","Thomas Jefferson","John Adams","Alexander Hamilton"],"correct_answer":"John Hancock"},"142":{"question":"What was the first Disney film that was produced in color?","choices":["Cinderella","Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs","Sleeping Beauty","Pocahontas"],"correct_answer":"Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs"},"143":{"question":"Sodium bicarbonate is used in the kitchen as what?","choices":["salt","sugar","baking soda","vinegar"],"correct_answer":"Baking soda"},"144":{"question":"In the 1983 movie National Lampoon’s Vacation, what is the name of the fictional amusement park the Griswold family is trying to go to?","choices":["Dorney Park","Walley World","Six Flags","Dollywood"],"correct_answer":"Walley World"},"145":{"question":"In Ray Bradbury’s novel Farenheit 451, what are they burning?","choices":["clothes","houses","books","money"],"correct_answer":"Books"},"146":{"question":"What was the first capital of the United States?","choices":["Washington, D.C.","Richmond","Boston","Philadelphia"],"correct_answer":"Philadelphia"},"147":{"question":"Which actor performs music under the stage name Childish Gambino?","choices":["Donald Glover","Will Smith","Frank Ocean","Tyler, The Creator"],"correct_answer":"Donald Glover"},"148":{"question":"Which water sport is the official sport for the state of Hawaii?","choices":["water polo","swimming","water skiing","surfing"],"correct_answer":"Surfing"},"149":{"question":"In the movie The Princess Bride, what is Westley’s response to the requests of Buttercup?","choices":["“Okay.”","“Of course, I love you.”","“As you wish.”","“Anything for you.”"],"correct_answer":"“As you wish.”"},"150":{"question":"What is the name of the company that published the Mario Kart video game?","choices":["Nintendo","Electronic Arts (EA)","SEGA","Xbox"],"correct_answer":"Nintendo"}}